

PROFILE

Experience in data analysis in the creation of dashboards for global projects for the financial area, in addition to creating the analysis and auditing of the data, using technological tools such as Power BI. I have carried out projects of great magnitude with teams around the world creating solutions for senior delivering management, category reports and positive KPIS. I have worked in payments of thousands of people in payroll and auditing them from different countries, having knowledge of different legislations in Costa Rica, Mexico, and the United States with amounts greater than 36 million dollars.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+506 -6021-8458

WEBSITE:

https://priscilamorales01.github.io **EMAIL**:

priscillamoralessegura@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Active learning new technologies Writer Baker Enjoy working out

PRISCILA MORALES

DATA ANALYST & PAYROLL SPECIALIST

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration Emphasis in Human Resources UNED

Specialist in Telecommunications and Networks. Universidad Politécnica Internacional

Teaching of English Universidad Hispanoamericana

CERTIFICATES

- Lean Six Sigma Yellow and Green Belt
- Power Bl
- Project Management
- Data Analysis
- Resilience
- Continues improvement
- E commerce
- Basic Merchandisina

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2022- CURRENT **AMAZON** Payroll Coordinator for MX: Owner of the termination process for Salary employees of AWS, ADS and VCS.

2019- JUNE 2022 **SMITH AND NEPHEW** Power BI Data Analyst and US Payroll Specialist: Owner of projects of Data Analysis, visualization of all the Payroll Global Department, Owner of the end-to-end US Payroll with amount greater than 36 millions of dollars.

2018-2019 **FORTIS INTEGRAL** Data and CR Payroll Analyst: Owner of the Costa Rica Payroll process end to end.

amazon Smith-Nephew

SKILLS

